# **Jack Kershaw**

jackkershaw@protonmail.co m linkedin.com/in/jackkershaw github.com/jones58 jackkershaw.net

I am a developer and designer who previously ran a graphic design studio. My desire to build custom digital tools has led me to spend the past two years learning the fundamentals of software development.

### **EDUCATION**

Twelve-week Web
Development Bootcamp
Just IT, 2023-2024

#### **BA Greek with Latin**

University College London (UCL), 2016-2020

A-Levels: Latin A, Ancient

Greek A, Maths B GCSEs: 6 A\*s, 3 As

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

**Frontend:** React, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, Tailwind, Node

**Backend:** Python and MySQL **Other:** Git (CLI and Github), Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Linux, Docker, Figma, Final Cut Pro, CMS (Squarespace, Wix and Blocs), Etsy and BigCartel

# **PROJECTS**

#### **London Brutalist Map**

brutalistmap.jackkershaw.net github.com/jones58/brutalist-map

- A project to help people discover London's Brutalist buildings.
- Built using Mapbox API, HTML, CSS and JavaScript.
- Currently rebuilding this project using Vite,
   React and TypeScript to enhance developer and user experience.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Director and Graphic Designer**

Tapir Studio Limited, 2019-2023

- Graphic design focusing on art direction and computer-based design of posters, social media branding and web design.
- Printed and distributed 200,000 posters and stickers in the UK and internationally.
- Enterprise management: registering at Companies' House, setting employment terms, distributing work, online sales and liaising with accountants and other outside parties.
- Client-facing role: acquiring customers,
   negotiating terms and providing client service.
- Clients included Oxford University, Fête de l'Humanité, Autonomy, Common Knowledge, among many others.
- In August 2022, subject of a full-page feature in the Observer.

#### **Video Editor**

Freelance, 2016 - 2022

- Created social media videos for the Labour Party, Momentum, The World Transformed, Just Treatment (NHS campaign) and Palestine Solidarity Campaign.
- Effective time management of projects and solving problems with clients.

#### **Sales Associate**

Cotswold Outdoor, Guildford, 2015 - 2016

- I worked in a team of sales assistants, offering help and advice to over fifty customers a day.